Center for Traditional Music and Dance collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series 2: Event documentation, 1968-2015
  - Events, 1981
    - Winter Folk Festival, December 1981
      - Sound Recordings, 1981-12-11 to 1981-12-12
        - 1 sound tape reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: WFF 81-1211_1_2a_rd
        - 1 sound tape reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: WFF 81-1211_2b_3_rd
        - 1 sound disc (CD), WFF 81-1211-1,2,3-TD (Box 18)
        - 1 sound reel: 7 in., AFC 2014/044: WFF 81-1211-12_1
        - 1 sound reel: 7 in., AFC 2014/044: WFF 81-1211-12_2
        - 1 sound reel: 7 in., AFC 2014/044: WFF 81-1211-12_3
        - 18 audio files (wav): digital., WFF81-1211-12-1_2_3-TD
    - Other events, 1981
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials
        - 1 folder, 1981-01-02, FDF 81-0102; Note on folder: Armenian Dance Workshop (Box-folder 3/57)
        - 1 folder, 1981-01-30, FDF 81-0130; Note on folder: Pontic Greek Workshop (Box-folder 3/58)
        - 1 folder, 1981-03-27, FDF 81-0227; Note on folder: Special Balkan Dance Workshop (Box-folder 3/59)
        - 1 folder, 1981-03-27, FDF 81-0327; Note on folder: Special Polish Dance Workshop (Box-folder 3/60)
        - 1 folder, 1981-04-10, BAC 81-0410; Note on folder: Lecture & Film with Raina Katsarova (Box-folder 3/61)
        - 1 folder, 1981-04-23, BAC 81-0423; Note on folder: St. Lazarus Day Celebration (Box-folder 3/62)
        - 1 folder, 1981-05-17, TOUR/JMT 81-0517; Note on folder: Klezmer Music in Two Worlds (Box-folder 3/63)
        - 1 folder, 1981-05-18, JMT 81-0518; Note on folder: Klezmer Music in Two Worlds (Box-folder 3/64)
        - 1 folder, 1981-05-29; 1981-06-26, ECMS 81-0529-0626; Note on folder: Macedonian Music; Epirot Music; Serbian Music (Box-folder 3/65)
        - 1 folder, 1981-05-31, TOUR/JMT 81-0531; Note on folder: Jewish Klezmer Music at Brighton Beach (Box-folder 3/66)
        - 1 folder, 1981-09-11, Note on folder: Opening Celebration at 179 Varick (Box-folder 4/3)
  - Events, 1982
    - Dave Tarras Interviews / Performance, April-May 1982
      - Moving Images, 1982-04-11
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: FR/I 82-0411_01
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: FR/I 82-0411_02; Note on media: Interviews with Efraim Tarras
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: FR/I 82-0411_03
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: FR/I 82-0411_04
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: FR/I 82-0411_05
        - 1 videocassette (DVCAM; 124 min.), AFC 2014/044: FR/I 82-0411_1-5; Note on media: Dave Tarras interview with Ethel Raim
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., FR/I 82-0411_1-5
      - Moving Images, 1982-05-13 to 1982-05-14
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: FR/I 82-0513_01
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: FR/I 82-0513_01
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: FR/I 82-0513_02
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: FR/I 82-0513_02
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: FR/I 82-0513_03
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: FR/I 82-0513_03
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: FR/I 82-0513_04
        - 1 videocassette (DVCAM; 124 min.), AFC 2014/044: FR/I 82-0513_D1-D3, FR/I 82-0514_D1-D3; Note on media: Dave Tarras interview with Ethel Raim
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., FR/I 82-0513_D1-D3, FR/I 82-0514_D1-D3; Note on media: interviews with Dave Tarras, Adel and Efraim Tarras
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., FR/I 82-0514_D1-D4; Note on media: Interviews with Dave Tarras, Efri and Adel
        - 1 videocassette (DVCAM; 124 min.), AFC 2014/044: FR/I 82-0514_D1-D4; Note on media: Dave Tarras Trio performance
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: FR/I 82-0514_01
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: FR/I 82-0514_01; Note on media: Dave Tarras interviews (with Efraim Tarras)
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: FR/I 82-0514_02; Note on media: Effie
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: FR/I 82-0514_02; Note on media: Dave Tarras interviews (with Efraim Tarras)
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: FR/I 82-0514_03
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: FR/I 82-0514_03; Note on media: Dave Tarras interviews (with Efraim Tarras and Adel)
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: FR/I 82-0514_04; Note on media: Adele
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: FR/I 82-0514_04; Note on media: Dave Tarras interviews (with Efraim Tarras and Adel)
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: FR 82-05xx_01; Note on media: Dave Tarras; Venue: Shady Nook
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: FR 82-05xx_02
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: FR 82-05xx_03
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: FR 82-05xx_04
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: FR 82-05xx_05
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: FR 82-05xx_06
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: FR 82-05xx_07
    - Recording Session: Orchestra Banatul, May 1982
      - Sound Recordings, 1982-05-08
        - 1 sound tape reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: RS 82-0508_1
        - 1 sound tape reel (29 min.): 10 in., AFC 2014/044: RS 82-0508_2
        - 1 sound tape reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: RS 82-0508_3
        - 1 sound tape reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: RS 82-0508_4
        - 1 sound tape reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: RS 82-0508_5
        - 1 sound tape reel (12 min.): 10 in., AFC 2014/044: RS 82-0508_6
        - 1 sound disc (CD), RS 82-0508-1,2,3a (Box 17)
        - 1 sound disc (CD), RS 82-0508-3b,4,5a (Box 17)
        - 1 sound disc (CD), RS 82-0510-5b,6 (Box 17)
        - 22 audio files (wav): digital., RS 82-0508-1_2_3a
        - 27 audio files (wav): digital., RS 82-0508-3b_4_5a
        - 2 audio files (wav): digital., RS 82-0508-5b_6
    - Recording Session: Manolis Papadopolous / Lazoros Papadopolous Orchestra, June 1982
      - Sound Recordings, 1982-06-13
        - 1 sound tape reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: RS 82-0613_1; Note on media: Manolis Papadopolous, Holy Trinity Church
        - 1 sound tape reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: RS 82-0613_2; Note on media: Manolis Papadopolous; Lazoros Papadopolous Orchestra
        - 1 sound tape reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: RS 82-0613_3; Note on media: Lazoros Papadopolous Orchestra
        - 1 sound disc (CD), RS 82-0613-1,2a; Note on media: CD dubs buy Art Shifrin, unindexed (Box 17)
        - 1 sound disc (CD), RS 82-0613-2b, 3; Note on media: CD dubs of RtR, no indexing (Box 17)
        - 2 audio files (wav): digital., RS82-0613-1_2a
        - 2 audio files (wav): digital., RS82-0613-2b_3
    - Winter Folk Festival / Greek Music Festival, December 1982
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, 1982-12-03
        - 1 folder, WFF 82-1203; Note on folder: Fifteenth Annual Winter Folk Festival (Box-folder 4/11)
      - Moving Images, 1982-12-03
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: WFF 82-1203_01; Note on media: Ilias Kementsides and Hristoforos Hristoforides (part 1)
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: WFF 82-1203_02; Note on media: Ilias Kementsides and Hristoforos Hristoforides (part 2; recorded 1982-12-01); Macedonian trio and dancers (part 1; 1982-12-02)
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: WFF 82-1203_03; Note on media: Macedonian trio and dancers (part 2; 1982-12-02)
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: WFF 82-1203_04; Note on media: Music presentation workshop #1: Cretan lyra and lauto (part 1)
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: WFF 82-1203_05; Note on media: Music presentation workshop #1: Cretan lyra and lauto (part 2)
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: WFF 82-1203_06; Note on media: Music presentation workshop #2 (part 1)
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: WFF 82-1203_07; Note on media: Music presentation workshop #2 (part 2); Music presentation workshop #3 (part 1)
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 30 min.), AFC 2014/044: WFF 82-1203_08; Note on media: Music presentation workshop #3 (part 2)
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 30 min.), AFC 2014/044: WFF 82-1203_09; Note on media: Music presentation workshop #3 (part 3)
      - Sound Recordings, 1982-12-04 to 1982-12-05
        - 1 sound reel: 7 in., AFC 2014/044: WFF 82-1204-1205_1
        - 1 sound reel: 7 in., AFC 2014/044: WFF 82-1204-1205_2
        - 1 sound reel: 7 in., AFC 2014/044: WFF 82-1204-1205_3
        - 1 sound reel: 7 in., AFC 2014/044: WFF 82-1204-1205_4
        - 1 sound reel: 7 in., AFC 2014/044: WFF 82-1204-1205_5
        - 1 sound tape reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: WFF 82-1204-1205_1_2a_rd
        - 1 sound tape reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: WFF 82-1204-1205_2b_3_rd
        - 1 sound tape reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: WFF 82-1204-1205_4_rd
        - 1 sound tape reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: WFF 82-1204-1205_5_rd
        - 1 sound disc (CD), WFF 82-1204-1205-1,2,3-TD; Note on media: 15th Annual Winter Folk Festival/Greek Music Tour (Box 18)
        - 1 sound disc (CD), WFF 82-1204-1205-4,5,6-TD; Note on media: RtR rolls 5 and 6 were switched in boxes. Thus they were dubbed out of order. However, as there was only 5 minutes on roll 6, it was added to the end of roll 5. Distortion on CD track 8 from orig. recording. (Box 18)
        - 19 audio files (wav): digital., WFF82-1204-05-1_2_3-TD
        - 8 audio files (wav): digital., WFF82-1204-05-4_5_6-TD
    - Recording Session: Theodore Kekes - Greek Thracian Bagpipes, December 1982
      - Sound Recordings, 1982-12-07
        - 1 sound reel: 7 in., AFC 2014/044: RS 82-1207_1
        - 1 sound reel: 7 in., AFC 2014/044: RS 82-1207_2
        - 1 sound reel: 7 in., AFC 2014/044: RS 82-1207_3
        - 1 sound reel: 7 in., AFC 2014/044: RS 82-1207_4
        - 1 sound reel: 7 in., AFC 2014/044: RS 82-1207_5
        - 1 sound reel: 7 in., AFC 2014/044: RS 82-1207_6
        - 1 sound disc (CD), RS 82-1207-1,2,3-TD (Box 17)
        - 1 sound disc (CD), RS 82-1207-4,5,6-TD (Box 17)
        - 25 audio files (wav): digital., RS82-1207-1_2_3-TD
        - 17 audio files (wav): digital., RS82-1207-4_5_6-TD
    - Recording Session: Macedonian Zurnas and Daouli, December 1982
      - Sound Recordings, 1982-12-09
        - 1 sound tape reel (polyester): 10 in., AFC 2014/044: RS 82-1209_1; Note on media: Holy Trinity Church, 341 E. 87th St., NY
        - 1 sound tape reel (polyester): 10 in., AFC 2014/044: RS 82-1209_2
        - 1 sound tape reel (polyester): 10 in., AFC 2014/044: RS 82-1209_3
        - 1 sound tape reel (polyester): 10 in., AFC 2014/044: RS 82-1209_4
        - 1 sound tape reel (polyester): 10 in., AFC 2014/044: RS 82-1209_5
        - 1 sound tape reel (polyester): 10 in., AFC 2014/044: RS 82-1209_6
        - 1 sound tape reel (polyester): 10 in., AFC 2014/044: RS 82-1209_7
        - 1 sound disc (CD), RS 82-1209-1, 2 (Box 17)
        - 1 sound disc (CD), RS 82-1209-3 (Box 17)
        - 1 sound disc (CD), RS 82-1209-4, 5 (Box 17)
        - 1 sound disc (CD), RS 82-1209-6, 7 (Box 17)
        - 2 audio files (wav): digital., RS82-1209-1_2
        - 1 audio file (wav): digital., RS82-1209-3
        - 2 audio files (wav): digital., RS82-1209-4_5
        - 2 audio files (wav): digital., RS82-1209-6_7
    - Other events, 1982
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials
        - 1 folder, 1982-02-21, FILM 82-0221; Note on folder: Eastern European Film (Box-folder 4/7)
        - 1 folder, 1982-06-05, QFF 82-0605; Note on folder: Queens Ethnic Music Festival (Box-folder 4/8)
        - 1 folder, 1982-06-06, TOUR/JMT 82-0606; Note on folder: Klezmer Music (Box-folder 4/9)
        - 1 folder, 1982-06-07, TOUR/JMT 82-0607; Note on folder: Klezmer Music in Two Worlds (Box-folder 4/10)
        - 1 folder, 1982-1983, GMT 82-83; Note on folder: Greek Music Tour (Box-folder 4/13)
        - 1 folder, 1982-1983, Note on folder: Folk Arts Pogram - NY State Council on the Arts (Box-folder 4/12)
      - Sound Recordings, 1982-12-01
        - 1 sound reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: RS 82-1201_1, 2a RD; Note on media: Unlabeled
        - 1 sound reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: RS 82-1201_2b, 3 RD; Note on media: Unlabeled
        - 1 sound reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: RS 82-1201_4, 5a RD; Note on media: Unlabeled
        - 1 sound reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: RS 82-1201_5b, 6 RD; Note on media: Unlabeled
  - Events, 1983
    - Italian Music Tour, June 1983
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, 1983-06-17
        - 1 folder, Note on folder: Musica Popolare (Box-folder 4/18)
      - Photographs, 1983-06-18 to 1983-07-03
        - 1 folder, Note on folder: Great Hudson River Revival; Italian Music Tour - Yonkers, NY; Williamsburg, Brooklyn (Box-folder 13/3)
      - Moving Images, 1983-06-30
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: TOUR-IMT 83-0630_01; Note on media: Musica Popolare. Venue: Wesleyan University
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: TOUR-IMT 83-0630_02; Note on media: Musica Popolare. Venue: Wesleyan University
      - Sound Recordings, 1983-06-27 to 1983-06-29
        - 1 sound reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: TOUR IMT 83-0627-29_1, 2a RD
        - 1 sound reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: TOUR IMT 83-0627-29_2b, 3 RD
        - 1 sound reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: TOUR IMT 83-0627-29_4, 5a RD
        - 1 sound reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: TOUR IMT 83-0627-29_5b, 6 RD
        - 1 sound reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: TOUR IMT 83-0627-29_7, 8 RD
        - 1 sound reel: 7 in., AFC 2014/044: TOUR-IMT 83-0627-29_1
        - 1 sound reel: 7 in., AFC 2014/044: TOUR-IMT 83-0627-29_2
        - 1 sound reel: 7 in., AFC 2014/044: TOUR-IMT 83-0627-29_3
        - 1 sound reel: 7 in., AFC 2014/044: TOUR-IMT 83-0627-29_4
        - 1 sound reel: 7 in., AFC 2014/044: TOUR-IMT 83-0627-29_5
        - 1 sound reel: 7 in., AFC 2014/044: TOUR-IMT 83-0627-29_6
        - 1 sound reel: 7 in., AFC 2014/044: TOUR-IMT 83-0627-29_7
        - 1 sound reel: 7 in., AFC 2014/044: TOUR-IMT 83-0627-29_8
        - 1 sound disc (CD), IMT 83-0627-29-1,2,3; Note on media: Colliano Village, Naples Region (Box 16)
        - 1 sound disc (CD), IMT 83-0627-29-4,5,6; Note on media: Colliano Village, Somma Vesuviano (Box 16)
        - 1 sound disc (CD), IMT 83-0627-29-1,7,8; Note on media: Somma Vesuviano (Box 16)
        - 34 audio files (wav): digital., Tour IMT83-0627-29-1_2_3-TD
        - 33 audio files (wav): digital., IMT83-0627-29-4_5_6
        - 23 audio files (wav): digital., Tour IMT83-0627-29-7_8-TD
    - Winter Folk Festival, December 1983
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, 1983-12-03
        - 1 folder, WFF 83-1203; Note on folder: Sixteenth Annual Winter Folk Festival (Box-folder 4/20)
      - Moving Images, 1983-12-03
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: WFF 83-1203_01; Note on media: Venue: Hunter College
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: WFF 83-1203_02; Note on media: Hunter College
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: WFF 83-1203_03; Note on media: Andy Statman; Ilias Kementzides
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: WFF 83-1203_04; Note on media: Ilias Kementzides; Cretans
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: WFF 83-1203_05; Note on media: Halkias Family Orchestra
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: WFF 83-1203_06; Note on media: Halkias Family Orchestra
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: WFF 83-1203_07; Note on media: Albanians from Waterbury, Patterson, NJ, Brooklyn
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: WFF 83-1203_08; Note on media: Hunter College
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: WFF 83-1203_09; Note on media: Hunter College
        - 1 videocassette (DVCAM; 124 min.), AFC 2014/044: WFF 83-1203_1-4; Note on media: Andy Statman; Ilias Kementzides; Cretans; Halkias
        - 1 videocassette (DVCAM; 124 min.), AFC 2014/044: WFF 83-1203_6-9; Note on media: Halkias; Albanians
    - Other events, 1983
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials
        - 1 folder, 1983-01-03, EMCS 83-0103; Note on folder: Dave Tarras Trio (Box-folder 4/14)
        - 1 folder, 1983-04-30, EMCS 83-0430; Note on folder: Concert of Central Asian Folk & Classical Music (Box-folder 4/15)
        - 1 folder, 1983-05-14, FILM 83-0514; Note on folder: Greek Ethnographic Films (Box-folder 4/16)
        - 1 folder, 1983-06-04, QFF 83-0604; Note on folder: Queens Ethnic Music Festival (Box-folder 4/17)
        - 1 folder, 1983-06-18, EMCS 83-0618; Note on folder: Papa Manteo & Manteo Sicilian Marionette Theatre (Box-folder 4/19)
      - Photographs
        - 1 folder, 1983, QFF 83; Note on folder: Domna Samiou's performing ensemble (Box-folder 12/3)
        - 1 folder, 1983-11-27, FR 83-1127; Note on folder: Cretan Dancers (Box-folder 14/5)
  - Events, 1984
    - Queens Ethnic Music Festival, June 1984
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, 1984-06-09
        - 1 folder, Note on folder: Ninth Annual Queens Ethnic Music Festival (Box-folder 4/21)
      - Moving Images, 1984-06-09
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 30 min.), AFC 2014/044: QFF 84-0609_01; Note on media: Evo Nas II
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: QFF 84-0609_02; Note on media: DeFranco Family; Venue: Bohemian Hall
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 30 min.), AFC 2014/044: QFF 84-0609_03; Note on media: John Rousos Part II and Crowd Scenes; Venue: Bohemian Hall
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: QFF 84-0609_04; Note on media: Halkias Family; Venue: Bohemian Hall
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 30 min.), AFC 2014/044: QFF 84-0609_05; Note on media: John Rousos; Venue: Bohemian Hall
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 30 min.), AFC 2014/044: QFF 84-0609_06; Note on media: John Berberian; Venue: Bohemian Hall
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 30 min.), AFC 2014/044: QFF 84-0609_08; Note on media: John Berberian; Venue: Bohemian Hall
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 30 min.), AFC 2014/044: QFF 84-0609_09; Note on media: Evo Nos Part I; Venue: Bohemian Hall
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 30 min.), AFC 2014/044: QFF 84-0609_10; Note on media: Defranco Family Part II; Venue: Bohemian Hall
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 30 min.), AFC 2014/044: QFF 84-0609_11; Note on media: Danillete Velestites and DeFranco Part II (?); Venue: Bohemian Hall
        - 1 videocassette (DVCAM; 124 min.), AFC 2014/044: QFF 84-0609_1-2-3-4-5; Note on media: 1: Evo Nas; 2: DeFranco Family; 3: John Roussos; 4: Halkias (out of sequence with program; ossibly three performers in between); 5: John Roussos
        - 1 videocassette (DVCAM; 124 min.), AFC 2014/044: QFF 84-0609_6-8-9-10-11; Note on media: 6 and 8: John Berberian Orchestra; 9: Evo Nas; 10: DeFranco; 11: Daullet e Veleshtes and DeFranco
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., QFF 84-0609; Note on media: Greek, Feidl Yudin, Zenska Penska, Macedonian
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., QFF 84-0609_1-2-3-4-5; Note on media: 1: Evo Nas; 2: DeFranco Family; 3: John Roussos; 4: Halkias (out of sequence with program; ossibly three performers in between); 5: John Roussos
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., QFF 84-0609_6-8-9-10-11; Note on media: 6 and 8: John Berberian Orchestra; 9: Evo Nas; 10: DeFranco; 11: Daullet e Veleshtes and DeFranco
    - Recording Session: Musica Populare, October 1984
      - Sound Recordings, 1984-10-23
        - 1 sound reel: 7 in., AFC 2014/044: RS 84-1023_1
        - 1 sound reel: 7 in., AFC 2014/044: RS 84-1023_2
        - 1 sound reel: 7 in., AFC 2014/044: RS 84-1023_3
        - 1 sound reel: 7 in., AFC 2014/044: RS 84-1023_4
        - 1 sound reel: 7 in., AFC 2014/044: RS 84-1023_5
        - 1 sound tape reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: RS 84-1023_1_2a_rd
        - 1 sound tape reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: RS 84-1023_2b_3_rd
        - 1 sound tape reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: RS 84-1023_4_5c_rd
        - 1 sound tape reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: RS 84-1023_5b_rd
        - 1 sound disc (CD), RS 84-1023-1,2,3-TD; Note on media: Many of these songs are also on IMT 83 and often sung with more gusto. Recordings are brighter as well. (Box 17)
        - 1 sound disc (CD), RS 84-1023-4,5-TD (Box 17)
        - 21 audio file (wav): digital., RS84-1023-1_2_3-TD
        - 10 audio files (wav): digital., RS84-1023-4_5-TD
    - Recording Session: Music of Naoussa and Greek Macedonia, November 1984
      - Sound Recordings, 1984-11-20
        - 1 sound tape reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: RS 84-1120_1_2_rd
        - 1 sound tape reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: RS 84-1120_3_4_5a_rd
        - 1 sound tape reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: RS 84-1120_5b_6_7_rd
        - 1 sound tape reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: RS 84-1120_8_9_rd
        - 1 sound disc (CD), RS 84-1120-1,2,3,4,5-TD; Note on media: Vangelis and Dimitrios Psathas: Music of Naoussa and Greek Macedonia (Box 17)
        - 1 sound disc (CD), RS 84-1120-6,7,8,9-TD; Note on media: Vangelis and Dimitrios Psathas: Music of Naoussa and Greek Macedonia (Box 17)
        - 18 audio files (wav): digital., RS84-1120-1_2_3_4_5-TD
        - 21 audio file (wav): digital., RS84-1120-6_7_8_9-TD
    - Other events, 1984
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials
        - 1 folder, 1984-09-08, Note on folder: Hungarian Gypsy Dance with Gustav Balzas (Box-folder 4/22)
        - 1 folder, 1984-10-10, IMT 84-1010; Note on folder: Musica Popolare (Box-folder 4/23)
        - 1 folder, 1984-10-16, IMT 84-1016; Note on folder: Musica Popolare (Box-folder 4/28)
        - 1 folder, 1984-12-14, WFF 84-1214; Note on folder: Winter Folk Festival (Box-folder 4/24)
        - 1 folder, 1984-12-15, Note on folder: NYU Dance Party Flier (Box-folder 4/25)
      - Photographs
        - 1 folder, 1984, TOUR IMT 84; Note on folder: Italian Music Tour (Box-folder 13/3)
  - Events, 1985
    - Queens Ethnic Music and Dance Festival, September 1985
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, 1985-09-14
        - 1 folder (Box-folder 4/27)
      - Moving Images, 1985-09-14
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: QFF 85-0914_01
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: QFF 85-0914_02
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: QFF 85-0914_03; Note on media: DeFranco
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: QFF 85-0914_04
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: QFF 85-0914_05; Note on media: Antonias Kokonas; Kostas Maris
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: QFF 85-0914_06
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: QFF 85-0914_07
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: QFF 85-0914_08
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: QFF 85-0914_09
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: QFF 85-0914_10; Note on media: John Berberian Orchestra
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: QFF 85-0914_11; Note on media: Halkias
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: QFF 85-0914_12
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: QFF 85-0914_13; Note on media: Crni Biseri
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: QFF 85-0914_14; Note on media: Defranco Family
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: QFF 85-0914_15; Note on media: Bukharan Jewish Ensemble / Antonias
        - 1 videocassette (U-matic; 20 min.), AFC 2014/044: QFF 85-0914_16; Note on media: Halkias Family Orchestra